// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
      question: "_expresses a real or an unreal conditions.",
      answer: "Conditional",
      options: [
        "Reason",
        "Condition",
        "Conditional",
        "Conversion"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
      question: "A conditional expresses that only happen when a certain condition is fulfilled.",
      answer: "Main clause",
      options: [
        "If-clause",
        "Main clause",
        "Is-clause",
        "Major clause",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "It states condition.",
      answer: "If-clause",
      options: [
        "If-clause",
        "Main clause",
        "Is-clause",
        "Major clause",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
      question: "It states the result.",
      answer: "Main clause",
      options: [
        "If-clause",
        "Main clause",
        "Is-clause",
        "Major clause",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
      question: "If the citizens have abide by the rules impose on them.",
      answer: "Mustn't",
      options: [
        "If-clause",
        "Main clause",
        "Is-clause",
        "Major clause",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
      question: " When If-clause is placed at the beginning.",
      answer: "A comma separates it from the maincaluse.",
      options: [
        "No comma is required",
        "It depend on the statement or sentence if nedds comma to separate.",
        "A comma separates it from the maincaluse.",
        "None of the above",
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
      question: " When the if-clause us placed at the end of the sentence.",
      answer: "No comma is required",
      options: [
        "No comma is required",
        "It depend on the statement or sentence if nedds comma to separate.",
        "A comma separates it from the maincaluse.",
        "None of the above"
      ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
      question: "Conditions have 2 kinds the real and _.",
      answer: "modal auxiliary or modal verb",
      options: [
        "Unreal",
        "Real",
        "Thruthful",
        "True",
      ]
  },
{
      numb: 9,
      question: "These conditions are categorized into four, namely...",
      answer: "Prohibition",
      options: [
        "first, second, fourth and fifth",
        "first, second, third and fourth",
        "zero, first, second, and third",
        "second, third, fourth, fifth",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
      question: "If the heat will continue to increase, the water will boil. What is the main clause.",
      answer: "must and have to",
      options: [
        "If the heat will continue to increase",
        "Will continue to increase",
        "The water will boil",
        "The heat will continue",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
      question: "Zero and first conditional is categorize as_.",
      answer: "Real",
      options: [
        "Unreal",
        "Real",
        "Thruthful",
        "True",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
      question: "Second and third conditional is categorized as.",
      answer: "Unreal",
      options: [
        "Unreal",
        "Real",
        "Thruthful",
        "True",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
      question: "It is used to talk about thing in the future will probably not going to happen.",
      answer: "Second conditional",
      options: [
        "Second conditional",
        "First conditional",
        "Zero conditional",
        "Third conditional",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
      question: "It is used when the result are true, like a scientific fact or general truths.",
      answer: "Zero conditional",
      options: [
        "Second conditional",
        "First conditional",
        "Zero conditional",
        "Third conditional",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
      question: "It is used when we regret something or imagine a past unreal situation.",
      answer: "Third conditional",
      options: [
        "Second conditional",
        "First conditional",
        "Zero conditional",
        "Third conditional",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
      question: "It is used when we talk about things that might happen in the future.",
      answer: "First conditional",
      options: [
        "Second conditional",
        "First conditional",
        "Zero conditional",
        "Third conditional",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
      question: "If we treat animals with care, their population will grow. What conditional is this?",
      answer: "First conditional",
      options: [
        "Second conditional",
        "First conditional",
        "Zero conditional",
        "Third conditional",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
      question: "If the babies cry, they are hungry.",
      answer: "Zero conditional",
      options: [
        "Second conditional",
        "First conditional",
        "Zero conditional",
        "Third conditional",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
      question: "What is this sentence express? 'since it's already evening, can we stay here overnight?'",
      answer: "Third conditional",
      options: [
        "Second conditional",
        "First conditional",
        "Zero conditional",
        "Third conditional",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
      question: "What is this sentence express? 'we shouldn't hurt someone'",
      answer: "Second conditional",
      options: [
        "Second conditional",
        "First conditional",
        "Zero conditional",
        "Third conditional",
    ]
  },	
  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];